<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<odoo>
    <template id="legal_advice" name="Legal Advice Sande">
        <t t-call="website.layout">
            <t t-set="pageName" t-value="'Legal Advice'"/>
            <div id="wrap">
                <div class="container mb48">
                    <div class="oe_structure">
                        <section data-snippet-id="title">
                            <h1 class="text-center">Legal Advice</h1>
                        </section>
                    </div>
                    <div class="oe_structure">
                        <section class="s_text_block">
                            <div class="container">
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb8 mt16">
                                        <h2>1. Aplication and property of <strong><span class="text-uppercase">SANDE Y DIAZ S.L.</span></strong></h2>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12">
                                        <p>
                                            The owner of this website <a class="text-primary" href="https://www.sandeydiaz.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow,noindex" title="SANDE Y DÍAZ, S.L. Website">
                                            <span>(www.sandeydiaz.com)</span></a> is <strong><span class="text-uppercase">SANDE Y DIAZ S.L.</span></strong>
                                            (hereinafter <strong>SANDE Y DÍAZ</strong>) established in St/ Nóvoa Santos, 11 baixo, 15006 A Coruña (Spain)
                                            and <a href="mailto:sandeydiaz@sandeydiaz.com" rel="noindex,nofollow" title="SANDE Y DÍAZ, S.L. email"><span class="text-primary">sandeydiaz@sandeydiaz.com</span></a>
                                            email address entered in the Register of A Coruña, Galicia, Spain ,Page 188, Book 241, Register 1, Page 849 and with Tax Identification Number B - 15033558.
                                        </p>
                                        <p>
                                            This website has been created to provide users with detailed information about <strong>SANDE Y DÍAZ</strong>
                                            , and, through various means, to contact and communicate with the company.
                                            It also provides the ability to access relevant information about products and services offered by <strong>SANDE Y DÍAZ</strong>.
                                            You can contact <strong>SANDE Y DÍAZ</strong> at the following email:
                                            <a href="mailto:sandeydiaz@sandeydiaz.com" rel="noindex,nofollow" title="SANDE Y DÍAZ, S.L. email"><span class="text-primary">sandeydiaz@sandeydiaz.com</span></a>.
                                        </p>
                                    </div>
                                </div>

                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb8">
                                        <h2>2. Legal Safeguard the following provisions govern the use of this site</h2>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12">
                                        <p>If you do not agree with them, please leave the site immediately.</p>
                                    </div>
                                </div>

                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb8">
                                        <h2>3. Topics of use and utilization of services </h2>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12">
                                        <h4 class="ml32"><strong>A. Obligation to make proper use of the service</strong></h4>
                                        <p class="ml32">
                                            The conditions of access to and use of this website is subject to applicable law
                                            and the principles of good faith and lawful use by the user of it being prohibited, in general, any action detrimental to
                                            <strong>SANDE Y DÍAZ</strong> and contrary to this disclaimer.
                                            The user agrees to use this service without engaging in activities that might be considered illicit or illegal,
                                            violating the rights of  <strong>SANDE Y DÍAZ</strong> or third parties,
                                            or which could damage, disable, overburden, or impair the service or prevent the normal use thereof by users.
                                        </p>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12">
                                        <h4 class="ml32"><strong>B. Content request</strong></h4>
                                        <p class="ml32">
                                            The user may not require any content available through this website, using means or procedures other
                                            than those that have been made available to or different from those normally used by Internet.
                                        </p>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12">
                                        <h4 class="ml32"><strong>C. Prohibitions</strong></h4>
                                        <p class="ml32">
                                            Is prohibited t he use of this website for illegal or unauthorized purposes, and specifically, but not limited to:
                                        </p>
                                        <ul>
                                            <li class="ml32 mt8 mb8">
                                                <p>Any form of violation of third party rights (right to privacy, image rights, intellectual property, etc..).</p>
                                            </li>
                                            <li class="ml32 mt8 mb8">
                                                <p>Making, using the contents of this website, all adverti sing and sending unsolicited emails (spam) or similar communication.</p>
                                            </li>
                                            <li class="ml32 mt8 mb8">
                                                <p>Introduce viruses, corrupted files, or any other similar software or programs that may damage the content or systems accessible through this website.</p>
                                            </li>
                                        </ul>
                                    </div>
                                </div>

                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb8">
                                        <h2>4. Intellectual property</h2>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb8">
                                        <p>
                                            The reproduction, distribution and public communication of the website are the property of <strong>SANDE Y DÍAZ</strong>.
                                            All text, designs, content, structure, databases, logos, fonts and other elements of the website are protected by law
                                            and international treaties on the matter.
                                            <strong>SANDE Y DÍAZ</strong> owns all intellectual property rights needed to operate the website and all of its components.
                                        </p>
                                        <p>
                                            Any reproduction, distribution, public communication, transformation or any other exploitation of all or part of web page content,
                                            made in any form or by any means, electronic, mechanical or otherwise is strictly prohibited.
                                            The violation of these rights will result in legal proceedings so relevant, civil and / or criminal penalties.
                                        </p>
                                        <p>
                                            <strong>SANDE Y DÍAZ</strong> owns the trademarks, logos and domain names related to services through its website,
                                            is strictly forbidden to reproduce or use authorized by the copyright owner.
                                        </p>
                                    </div>
                                </div>

                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb8">
                                        <h2>5. Data protection</h2>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb8">
                                        <p>
                                            According to the spanish Organic Law 15/1999, of December 13 th,
                                            Protection of Personal Data, we inform you that, your personal data will be used by <strong>SANDE Y DÍAZ</strong>
                                            to process your application and will be treated confidential computerized so.
                                            We understand that you consent to the transfer of data for commercial purposes and statistics to <strong>SANDE Y DÍAZ</strong>.
                                            If not, please inform us. You have the right at any time to refuse, cancel and rectify the data concerning to you,
                                            contained in our databases, addressing <strong>SANDE Y DÍAZ</strong> through
                                            <a href="mailto:sandeydiaz@sandeydiaz.com" rel="noindex,nofollow" title="SANDE Y DÍAZ, S.L. email"><span class="text-primary">sandeydiaz@sandeydiaz.com</span></a>
                                            email address, or at the following address: <strong>SANDE Y DÍAZ</strong> - St / Nóvoa Santos, 11 baixo, 15006 A Coruña (Spain), duly crediting your personality.
                                        </p>
                                    </div>
                                </div>

                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb8">
                                        <h2>6. Limitation of liability</h2>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb8">
                                        <p>
                                            The user is solely responsible for any infringements which may be incurred or any damage they may cause to others by the misuse or illegal use of the website.
                                        </p>
                                        <p>
                                            <strong>SANDE Y DÍAZ</strong> not be liable for any loss or damage resulting from interference, omissions, interruptions, computer viruses,
                                            telephone breakdowns or disconnections in the operation of the computer or electronic system, caused by reasons beyond the Company,
                                            delays or blockages in the use of these systems caused by deficiencies or overloads of telephone lines,
                                            overloads on the Internet system or other electronic systems.
                                        </p>
                                        <p>
                                            The links from this site to other sites controlled by other parties, <strong>SANDE Y DÍAZ</strong>
                                            is not responsible for the contents of any site or at you can link or the consequences that this entails.
                                            Users make use of hyperlinks at their own risk. Links that may appear on the website to other websites are provided
                                            for information purposes only and do not imply any associati on with the linked sites, nor a recommendation of goods or services offered by these sites.
                                        </p>
                                        <p>
                                            <strong>SANDE Y DÍAZ</strong> does not guarantee the condition or legality of content or adequate provision of services offered to users by third parties,
                                            which can be accessed thro ugh the links. Nor is it responsible for the hyperlinks that customers can create through their websites.
                                            <strong>SANDE Y DÍAZ</strong> disclaims liability for external third - party cookies that they can install on the hard drive of the user's computer.
                                        </p>
                                        <p>
                                            Nor will result <strong>SANDE Y DÍAZ</strong> responsibility for inaccuracies or typographical errors that can be seen in the content of its site.
                                        </p>
                                    </div>
                                </div>

                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb8">
                                        <h2>7. Services</h2>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb8">
                                        <p>
                                            <strong>SANDE Y DÍAZ</strong> reserves the right to grant access to its website, without notice, at its discretion and temporal,
                                            and the right to modify, update, at any time and without notice, presentation, legal notice, conditions, or using the website and the contents thereof,
                                            and in any case, with respect to the applicable standards.
                                        </p>
                                    </div>
                                </div>

                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb8">
                                        <h2>8. Privacy policy</h2>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb8">
                                        <h4 class="ml32"><strong>What are cookies?</strong></h4>
                                        <p class="ml32">
                                            A cookie is a file that is downloaded to your computer / smartphone / tablet or device to access certain web pages.
                                            These cookies allow our website, among other things , store and retrieve information about browsing habits of a user or your computer,
                                            depending on the information it contains and the way you use your computer, can be used to recognize an user.
                                        </p>
                                        <h4 class="ml32 mt16"><strong>What types of cookies used this site?</strong></h4>
                                        <ul class="list-unstyled ml32">
                                            <li class="ml32 mt16">
                                                <p><strong>Technical Cookies:</strong></p>
                                            </li>
                                            <ul class="list-unstyled">
                                                <li class="ml32 mt8 mb8">
                                                    <p>
                                                        These are created and managed solely by us, and allow the user to navigate through our website and use of the various options,
                                                        for example, identify the session, personalize information, or access restricted areas.
                                                    </p>
                                                </li>
                                            </ul>
                                            <li class="ml32 mt16">
                                                <p><strong>Analysis Cookies:</strong></p>
                                            </li>
                                            <ul class="list-unstyled">
                                                <li class="ml32 mt8 mb8">
                                                    <p>
                                                        Those which, either by us or by third parties, quantify the number of users,
                                                        and make a measurement and statistical analysis of ho w users use the service offered.
                                                        Thus navigation is discussed on our website, in order to improve the supply of products or services that we offer.
                                                    </p>
                                                </li>
                                            </ul>
                                        </ul>
                                        <h4 class="ml32 mt16"><strong>How do you disable cookies?</strong></h4>
                                        <p class="ml32">
                                            You can allow, block or delete cookies installed on your computer by configuring your browser settings installed on your computer.
                                        </p>
                                    </div>
                                </div>

                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb8">
                                        <h2>9. Governing law and jurisdiction</h2>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb8">
                                        <p>
                                            The terms and conditions governing this site, and the relations arising from the same,
                                            are protected and are subject to Spanish law. For the resolution of any controversy,
                                            dispute or disagreement that may arise between you and <strong>SANDE Y DÍAZ</strong> from the use of this website,
                                            user is subject to the jurisdiction of the courts of A Coruña (Galicia, Spain),
                                            with express waiver by user of any other jurisdiction that may correspond.
                                        </p>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </section>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div class="oe_structure"/>
        </t>
    </template>
</odoo>