<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<odoo>
    <template id="legal_terms" name="Legal Terms of use Sande">
        <t t-call="website.layout">
            <t t-set="pageName" t-value="'Terms of Sale'"/>
            <div id="wrap">
                <div class="container mb48">
                    <div class="oe_structure">
                        <section data-snippet-id="title">
                            <h1 class="text-center">Terms of Sale</h1>
                        </section>
                    </div>
                    <div class="oe_structure">
                        <section class="s_text_block">
                            <div class="container">
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb8 mt16">
                                        <h2>Legal Safeguard</h2>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12">
                                        <p>
                                            Please read these Terms of Sale ("Terms", "Terms of Sale") carefully before using the
                                            <a t-att-href="res_company.website" target="_blank" rel="nofollow,noindex" title="Sitio web de SANDE Y DÍAZ, S.L."><span t-field="res_company.website"/></a>
                                            website (the "Service") operated by ​<strong><span class="text-uppercase" t-field="res_company.name"/></strong>
                                            ("us", "we", or "our").
                                        </p>
                                        <p>
                                            Your access to and use of the Service is conditioned on your acceptance of and compliance with these Terms.
                                            These Terms apply to all visitors, users and others who access or use the Service.
                                        </p>
                                        <p>
                                            By accessing or using the Service you agree to be bound by these Terms.
                                            If you disagree with any part of the terms then you may not access the Service.
                                        </p>
                                    </div>
                                </div>

                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb8">
                                        <h2>Use of Services</h2>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12">
                                        <h4 class="ml32"><strong>Obligation to make correct use of the service</strong></h4>
                                        <p class="ml32">
                                            The conditions of access and use of this website are subject to current legislation and the principles of
                                            good faith and lawful use by the user of the same being prohibited, in general, any action in
                                            to the detriment of <strong><span class="text-uppercase" t-field="res_company.name"/></strong> and contrary to this legal notice.
                                            The user agrees to use this service without engaging in activities that may be considered unlawful or illegal, in violation of
                                            <strong><span class="text-uppercase" t-field="res_company.name"/></strong> rights
                                            or third parties, or that could damage, disable, overload or deteriorate the Service or prevent its normal use by other users.
                                        </p>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12">
                                        <h4 class="ml32"><strong>Content Request</strong></h4>
                                        <p class="ml32">
                                            The user will not be able to demand any type of content available through this website, using
                                            means or procedures other than those made available to them or other than those used usually over the Internet.
                                        </p>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12">
                                        <h4 class="ml32"><strong>Prohibitions</strong></h4>
                                        <p class="ml32">
                                            Use of this website for illegal or unauthorized purposes is prohibited and, specifically, but not limited to:
                                        </p>
                                        <ul>
                                            <li class="ml32 mt8 mb8">
                                                Any form of violation of the rights of third parties (right to privacy, self-image, intellectual property rights, etc.).
                                            </li>
                                            <li class="ml32 mt8 mb8">
                                                Perform, using the content of this website, all advertising and sending unsolicited emails (spam) or similar communications.
                                            </li>
                                            <li class="ml32 mt8 mb8">
                                                Introduce viruses, damaged files, any other similar software or programs that may
                                                unauthorized damage or alteration of the contents or systems accessible through this website.
                                            </li>
                                        </ul>
                                    </div>
                                </div>

                                 <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb8">
                                        <h2>Termination</h2>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12">
                                        <p>
                                            We may terminate or suspend access to our Service immediately, without prior notice or liability,
                                            for any reason whatsoever, including without limitation if you breach the Terms.
                                        </p>
                                        <p>
                                            All provisions of the Terms which by their nature should survive termination shall survive
                                            termination, including, without limitation, ownership provisions,
                                            warranty disclaimers, indemnity and limitations of liability.
                                        </p>
                                    </div>
                                </div>

                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb8">
                                        <h2>Links To Other Web Sites</h2>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12">
                                        <p>
                                            From links from this site to other third party sites, ​<strong><span class="text-uppercase" t-field="res_company.name"/></strong> does not
                                            responsible for the contents of any site or to which the user may link or the consequences that this entail.
                                            Users make use of hyperlinks at their own risk. The links that may appear on the site
                                            web to other websites have been established for purely informative purposes and do not involve any association
                                            with the linked sites, nor recommendation of the goods or services offered by these sites.
                                            ​<strong> <span class="text-uppercase" t-field="res_company.name"/></strong> no guarantees neither the conditions
                                            nor the legality of the contents or the adequate provision of the services offered to the
                                            users by third parties, which can be accessed through links. Nor is he responsible for the
                                            hyperlinks that your customers can create through their websites.
                                        </p>
                                        <p>
                                            We strongly advise you to read the terms and conditions and privacy policies of any third­party web sites or services that you visit.
                                        </p>
                                    </div>
                                </div>

                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb8">
                                        <h2>Governing Law</h2>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12">
                                        <p>
                                            The terms and conditions that govern this website, as well as the relationships that may arise from it
                                            same, they are protected and are subject to <span t-field="res_company.country_id.name"/> law.
                                            For the resolution of any type of controversy, litigation or discrepancy that may arise between the user and
                                            ​<strong> <span class="text-uppercase" t-field="res_company.name"/></strong> for the use of this website,
                                            shall be subject, for the resolution thereof, to the jurisdiction and jurisdiction of the courts of the
                                            <t t-if="res_company.city"><span t-field="res_company.city"/></t><t t-else="">Coruña</t>
                                            , with express resignation by the user of any other forum that may correspond to him.
                                        </p>
                                        <p>
                                            Our failure to enforce any right or provision of these Terms will not be considered a waiver of those rights.
                                            These Terms constitute the entire agreement between us regarding our Service, and supersede and replace
                                            any prior agreements we might have between us regarding the Service.
                                        </p>
                                    </div>
                                </div>

                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12 mb8">
                                        <h2>Changes</h2>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="row">
                                    <div class="col-md-12">
                                        <p>
                                            ​<strong><span class="text-uppercase" t-field="res_company.name"/></strong>
                                            reserves the right to give access to its website, without prior notice, at its discretion and
                                            temporary, and the right to modify, update, modify unilaterally, at any time and without notice,
                                            the submission, legal notice, terms of service, or use of the Website and its contents, and in any
                                            case, with respect to the applicable rules.
                                        </p>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </section>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
            <div class="oe_structure"/>
        </t>
    </template>
</odoo>